[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What substance is added to blood to keep it from clotting until it is needed?", "correct_answer": "Salt", "incorrect_answers": ["Sugar", "Ethanol", "Mecurium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The US is one of the leading countries in the number plastic surgery procedures.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Select the year in which these vents took place: Petroleum production began in the Middle East, the Cubs beat the Tigers in the World Series, and the Montreal Wanderers won the Stanley Cup.", "correct_answer": "1908", "incorrect_answers": ["1924", "1916", "1932"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 1995 comedy film Jim Carrey plays a crazy detective who is in hot pursuit of a rare white bat.", "correct_answer": "Ace Ventura: When Nature Calls", "incorrect_answers": ["Liar, Liar", "Dumb and Dumber", "Ace Ventura: Pet Detective"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At wedding ceremonies in Iran, this object is placed between two candelabras on a spread, to represent  the brightly future of the couple.", "correct_answer": "Mirror", "incorrect_answers": ["Silver plate", "Lamp", "Diamond ring"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Long Duk Dong", "correct_answer": "Sixteen Candles", "incorrect_answers": ["European Vacation", "Weird Science", "Planes, Trains  Automobiles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish the popular quote by the great Greek philosopher Aristotle: \u2018There was never a genius without a tincture of\u2026\u2019.", "correct_answer": "Madness", "incorrect_answers": ["Sorrow", "Scepticism", "Foolishness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Arsenic and Old Lace, what is the name of the book Mortimer was working on?", "correct_answer": "Mind over Matrimony", "incorrect_answers": ["Sex in the City", "Till Death Do Us Part", "Love and Lies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This breed of cat has a round head, large round eyes and very small ears bended forward and downward.", "correct_answer": "Scottish Fold", "incorrect_answers": ["American Curl", "Toyger", "Ussuri"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is the 12th Sign of the Chinese Zodiac.  It is a Yin Sign associated with the Water Element.", "correct_answer": "Pig", "incorrect_answers": ["Snake", "Rabbit", "Rat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The calendula, or marigold and the opal are the symbols of this month.", "correct_answer": "October", "incorrect_answers": ["November", "February", "June"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "James Bond is first to discover that which of these is Biofelds goal in the 1967 movie, You Only Live Twice?", "correct_answer": "Cause a US - Soviet war", "incorrect_answers": ["Halt the Japanese space program", "Build missile launch site", "Take control of  world economy"]}]